<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Crypto Portal</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tweets</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Price</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Words</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4">Media</string>
    <string name="tab_text_5"></string>



    <string name="url">https://restapiforapp.herokuapp.com/</string>


    <string name="info_all">
        "\u2022" Realtime filtered stream of crypto tweets from accounts with more than 100 thousand followers. \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="info_alts">
        "\u2022" Tracking the official accounts of the top cryptocurrencies. \n \n
        "\u2022" Engagement deviation score.. \n \n
        "\u2022" Filter for new pinned tweet, keywords match or exceptional engagement.\n \n
    </string>

    <string name="info_keywords_altcoins">
        "\u2022" Tracking the number of mentioning certain altcoin keywords in every tweet. \n \n
        "\u2022" Each candle represent 15 min real time data compared to 500 period moving average. \n \n
        "\u2022" Scale option: scale with the number of author followers. \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="info_keywords_bitcoin">
        "\u2022" Tracking the number of mentioning crypto keywords in every tweet. \n \n
        "\u2022" Scale option: scale with number of author followers. \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="info_breaking">
        "\u2022" Channel for breaking news. Political and business announcements from aggregated reporter lists. \n \n
        "\u2022" Display all news or just crypto oriented.
    </string>

    <string name="info_news">
        "\u2022" News aggregator for the most crypto articles on the web. \n \n
        "\u2022" Top stories for the latest hours.
    </string>

    <string name="info_vid">
        "\u2022" List of the most recent videos from the top crypto youtube channels.
</string>

    <string name="info_events">
        "\u2022" Upcoming events for the top altcoins.
    </string>

    <string name="resume">

        Crypto Portal is an app for enthusiasts or traders, who want to be up to date
        with the latest events, trends or news around bitcoin. The application scans all sources of crypto news:
social media, video channels, breaking news channels, altcoin events and web articles, all in real time.


In Crypto Portal you can find : \n \n
   "\u2022" List of the upcoming altcoin events. \n
   "\u2022" Keyword trends for altcoins and bitcoin. \n
   "\u2022" Greed and fear index. \n
   "\u2022" Aggregated channel for breaking news or announcements. \n
   "\u2022" Constant stream of all tweets, containing crypto keywords, filtered by number of followers. \n
   "\u2022" Monitor the social media accounts of the top cryptocurrencies for announcements or partnerships. \n
   "\u2022" Live list of the latest, top crypto videos. \n
   "\u2022" Top crypto web articles from the last hours. \n
   "\u2022" Price deviation from whole crypto sector. \n
   "\u2022" Engagement deviation for tweets from altcoin accounts. \n
   "\u2022" Alarms so you never miss an important event. \n


</string>

    <string-array name="spinner">
        <item>Small</item>
        <item>Medium</item>
        <item>Big</item>
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Default</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_loading_screen">loading_screen</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>

</resources>